(Amy:)to flaunt her sexuality
in order to get ahead.
(Penny:)Okay, what's the big deal?
(Penny:)Look, if it helps me make
a sale with a physician,
(Penny:)I don't think it hurts
to flirt a little.
(Penny:)I mean, laugh at their joke,
touch their arm,
(Penny:)maybe crank up the AC
in the car beforehand, you know,
(Penny:)to wake up the girls.
(Amy:)Maybe it's different
in the world of sales,
(Amy:)but it's already hard enough
(Amy:)for women to be taken seriously
in science.
(Bernadette:)I was kind of excited
about the article,
(Bernadette:)but now you're making me
feel bad.
(Penny:)No, I think you should do
whatever you want.
(Penny:)You know, maybe
if fashion magazines had
(Bernadette:)female scientists
in them,
(Penny:)I would've become
a theoretical physicist.
(Penny:)Stop smirking
at each other.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪